http://clevermedia.com/privacy.html

Mobile Apps
Sites
About
CleverMedia, Inc. Privacy Statement
CleverMedia, Inc., and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. We do not collect information for any marketing purposes at all. No membership or sign-up is required for playing any of the games on our sites. All of our ads are served by Google. Read their Privacy & Terms.
Mobile Game Apps: Several of our apps use Apple's GameCenter system for high scores. Our Island Golf game uses Apple's GameCenter for nicknames, but uses our own server to compile daily high score boards. Your GameCenter name and ID are recorded this purpose only and not used in any other way. No other personal data is collected. You can find Apple's GameCenter terms and conditions and privacy policy here.
GameScene.com High Score Boards: At this site, you can submit your score using your Facebook ID. No other information is recorded and this is only used for the purposes of displaying high scores.
CleverMedia, Inc. does not collect email addresses or any other information about our visitors except where specified above.
COPPA Compliance: CleverMedia, Inc. is required by law to provide you with the following information:
There is a link to the site's privacy policy (this page) on the home page of each of CleverMedia, Inc. sites.
There is a a link to the site's privacy policy on each page where personal information is collected. However, no personal information collected on any of our pages.
Here is a disclosure of the types of personal information we collect from children and how our site uses that information: We don't collect ANY information from children.
Here is a disclosure in about whether the personal information we collect from children is shared with third parties, and, if so, how the third parties use the information: We don't collect ANY information from children or anyone else, so we don't have any information to share.
Here is a disclosure in that parents have the right to review and delete any personal information your site previously collected from their child: We don't collect ANY information from children or anyone else, so we don't have any information that parents can review or delete.
Here is the contact information for our website operator: email us. See the bottom of this page for complete contact information.
Advertising at GameScene and Other Game Sites and Apps:
CleverMedia, Inc.'s sites use Google's AdSense network to serve ads when you visit our Web sites. Google also may separately place or recognize cookie files on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site.
Google may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can find out more here: Google's Privacy & Terms, How Google uses cookies in advertising.
In addition, please note:
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
CONTACT INFORMATION
If you have any further questions, please contact us.
According to law, we must provide complete contact information in our privacy policay. This information is provided for privacy policy issues ONLY. If you use this to SPAM us or send us unsolicited mail or make unsolicited phone calls, we will take appropriate action.
Email address: We have provided a link to a form where you can email us. Use this form. However, because the law is unclear whether this is enough, we need to provide an email address here. Because SPAM software will search this page, pick up this email address, and SPAM us, we will provide a special email address only for privacy policy inquiries: privacy2(at)clevermedia(dot)com. Notice that I have replaced the @ symbol with (at) and the . with (dot) so that the email can't be harvested by spammers from this page. If anyone uses this special email address to send us SPAM, we will take appropriate action according to federal and state laws.
Mailing address: CleverMedia Inc., P.O. Box 200803, Denver, CO 80220, USA. Do not send us junk mail.
Copyright 1995-2020 CleverMedia, Inc.
